Finding aid for Walter W. Marquardt Papers, 1896-1952
Bentley Historical Library
- Miscellaneous
  - Slide notecards (Box 7)
  - Speech notecards (Box 7)
  - Sound Recording (Box 7)
    [Digitized audio files are currently available only in the Bentley Historical Library reading room on designated Bentley Library computers.]
    - Marquardt Radio Speech To Phillipines, 1945 February 28; Audio Cassette, Compact Cassette, 1 7/8 ips (Box 7)
      - [Side 1; no Side 2], [91421-SR-1-1]; mp3 file; (W.W. Marquardt speech to the Philippines transmitted by Office of War Information Feb. 28, 1945 to mark the liberation of Manila from Japanese troops.)
- Bound reports, etc.
  - Bound reports, etc. (Box 8)